http://www.tmctransformers.com/privacy-policy

Data Controller and Owner
TMC Transformers S.p.A.
sales@tmctransformers.com
Privacy Policy
This website collects some information and personal data of its browsing users.
Collected data
The data collected by this website may be cookies, personal data, information requests, usage data, email address and other types of data.
The collected data may be entered manually by the user in the various forms on the website or through the navigation of the same.
Any use of cookies aims to identify the user by recording his navigation preferences to enable the provision of the requested service.
The lack of some user-compiled data may prevent the delivery of requested services .
You assume all responsibilities of all the data provided by third parties published or shared through this website and warrant that you have the right to communicate / disseminate them, releasing from any liability to third parties the holder of this site
Handling of collected data
Methods
The holder of the data provided on the site is committed to adopting the safety measures to prevent the disclosure and every kind of processing of personal data.
The handling is done through computer and telematic tools, with related methods to the stated purpose.
The data could be used by persons assigned for the management / organization of the site and by external actors (technical service providers, carriers, providers, communication and marketing agencies) appointed in charge of treatment by the website owner.
You may at any time request the updated list of responsible parties of data treatment from the Data Owner.
Place
User data are processed at the operational headquarters of the owner and everywhere else involved in data processing.
For more information contact the owner directly.
Times
The data are processed in the time needed to perform the requested services, or the purposes described in this document.
The user may at any time require discontinuation of treatment and the cancellation of their data.
Purpose
The purpose of user data collected allow the owner of this website to provide their services, and for other purposes such as statistical analysis, interaction with social networks, the use of external platforms and contact you.
Variuous types of data are collected, listed below:
CONTACT FORM AND INFORMATION REQUEST
Through the contact forms on this website, you consent to the use of data to meet various demands like more information, contact, quote and any other information specified in the relevant form.
Various types of data are collected.
NEWSLETTER, MAILING LIST, DEM
Through the contact forms on this website, you consent to the use for email messages containing information of various commercial or promotional nature.
Various types of data are collected.
INTERACTION WITH SOCIAL NETWORK
From the pages of this site you can make interactions with social networks
Each type of interaction and information acquired are subject to the settings of the user's privacy on the use of social networks, and in case the user dont's use that particular service, the social network could collect traffic data.
FACEBOOK
The “Like” button and Facebook social widgets are interactive services of the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
GOOGLE
The +1 button and Google+ social widgets are interactive services of the Google+ social network, provided by Google Inc.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
TWITTER
The tweet button and the Twitter social widgets are interactive services of the Twitter social network, provided by Twitter Inc.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here https://twitter.com/privacy
LINKEDIN
The button and LinkedIn social widgets are interactive services of the LinkedIn social network, provided by LinkedIn Inc.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
ADDTHIS
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy
CRITEO
The advertising service Crites is provided by Criteo SA and allows the display of targeted advertisments based on the user's browsing behaviour or possibly on interests. Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is FRANCE, you can view the policy here http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy/ and you can disable it from here http://www.criteo.com/deactivate-criteo-banners/
FACEBOOK REMARKETING
Facebook Remarketing is a behavioral targeting e remarketing service, provided by Facebook Inc.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
Google Analytics is a statistics service for websites and web applications provided by Google Inc.
Personal data is collected in order to analyze the statistics of access to the site and may be used by other Google services such as those to customize advertisements of its network.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ and you can disable it from here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
FACEBOOK ADS TRACKING PIXEL
Tracking pixel allows to monitor conversions from Facebook Ads, which is a statistical service provided by Facebook Inc.
This service is meant to connect the actions made by the user when browsing this site with data from Facebook.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
GOOGLE ADWORDS TRACKING PIXEL
Tracking pixel allows to monitor conversions from Google Adwords Ads, which is a statistical service provided by Google Inc.
This service is meant to connect the actions performed by the user when browsing this site with data from the Google advertising network.
Cookies and usage data are collected, data processing location is USA, you can view the policy here http://www.google.com/intl/it/policies/privacy/
Defense in court
The user data collected can be used for defense by the owner in court or in further steps for the establishment of abuse in the usage or related services from the user.
The user declares to be aware that the owner may disclose the data collected at the request of public authorities.
Further specifications
The user could request to provide more information for the collection and processing of their data in specific applications on this website.
Log files
This website uses the system log and third party logs which record user interactions and may also contain data such as your IP.
More information not indicated in this document
At any time the user can request more information on the processing of personal data to the data using the contact information on this site.
Exercise of rights by users
Users to whom the collected data refer have the right at any time to request confirmation of such data to the data owner, to know the contents and verify the correctness and ask for a possible integration, updating, modification and blocking of their data processed in violation of the law, and also to oppose for legitimate reasons to their treatment.
Any such requests should be addressed to the data controller.
This site does not support "do not track" requests, if you want more information you should consult the policies of third party services used in this website.
Changes to this privacy policy
At any time, the process owner reserves the right to make any changes to this document and to give publication on this page.
Check regularly at the bottom of this document the date of last modification.
If you do not accept the changes, you can always ask the owner of the treatment the cancellation of your data and not to use this site.
About this Privacy Policy
The data controller is responsible for this privacy policy.
This statement in fulfillment of the obligations under Article 10 of Directive number 95/46 / EC and 2002/58 / EC, as in the case of cookies by 2009/136 / EC
Document updated on 25/02/2016
Please, Fill in the form to Download INDUSTRY SERIES brochure
INDUSTRIA ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download POWERGEN SERIES brochure
POWERGEN ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download MARINE & OFFSHORE SERIES brochure
MARINA & OFFSHORE ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
ACCESSORI ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Company
*
Country
*
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
E-mail
*
Do you want to subscribe to our newsletter?
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download VPI SERIES brochure
VPI ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download COPPER WINDINGS SERIES brochure
SERIE AVVOLGIMENTI IN RAME ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download REDUCED LOSSES SERIES brochure
SERIE REDUCED LOSSES ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download STANDARD LOSSES SERIES brochure
SERIE STANDARD LOSSES ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Please, Fill in the form to Download ECOFRIENDLY SERIES brochure
SERIE ECOFRIENDLY ENG
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Name
*
Surname
*
Country
*
Afghanistan
Albania
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Company
*
E-mail
*
Newsletter
I want to subscribe to your newsletter
I accept terms and privacy conditions
*
I accept
SUBMIT
X
Utilizziamo i cookie per essere sicuri che tu possa avere la migliore esperienza sul nostro sito. Continuando la navigazione acconsenti al loro impiego.OkLeggi di più
